[The Tower of Whispers]
[برج الهمسات]
[Episode 3]
[الحلقة 3]
Hurry up!
عجلوا!
Stop!
قف!
Get up! Get up now!
انهض! انهض الآن!
No. 5! Get up now!
رقم ٥! انهض الآن!
Why did he stop?
لماذا توقف؟
Young man, what's going on?
يا شاب ماذا يحدث؟
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Why did he stop?
لماذا توقف؟
Miss, what displeased you?
آنسة، ما الذي أزعجك؟
He didn't deserve
لم يستحق
such a quick death.
موت سريع جدًا.
I want to buy him.
أريد أن أشتريه.
Before you die,
قبل أن تموت،
I will return all the suffering
سأعيد كل المعاناة
I endured in my past life to you.
لقد تحملت في حياتي الماضية لك.
Why is he chained up?
لماذا هو مقيد؟
I don't know.
لا أعرف.
What's happening?
ماذا يحدث؟
He must have offended someone.
لابد أنه أساء إلى شخص ما.
My Lady,
سيدتي،
why did you chain him up outside?
لماذا قمت بتقييده بالخارج؟
There are many people watching on the street.
هناك الكثير من الناس يشاهدون في الشارع.
Are we going too far?
هل نحن نذهب بعيدا جدا؟
I want him to taste
أريده أن يتذوق
the feeling of being humiliated in public.
الشعور بالإذلال أمام الجمهور.
[Lu's Mansion]
[قصر لو]
My Lady, I'll get you a mounting block.
سيدتي، سأحضر لك كتلة التركيب.
No need.
لا حاجة.
You, come here.
أنت، تعال هنا.
Kneel.
اركع.
Hold out your hands.
مد يديك.
Clean the blood off yourself before coming in.
قم بتنظيف الدم عن نفسك قبل الدخول.
[Lu's Mansion]
[قصر لو]
You're filthy.
أنت قذر.
That's my residence ahead.
هذا هو مقر إقامتي في الأمام.
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدا،
whether it's windy, rainy, or freezing cold,
سواء كان الجو عاصفًا أو ممطرًا أو باردًا جدًا،
your residence
مكان إقامتك
is right on this floor beneath my feet.
هو على هذه الأرض تحت قدمي.
Be a good watchdog for me.
كن حارسًا جيدًا لي.
Master,
يتقن،
please give me a name.
من فضلك أعطني اسمًا.
Why does a slave need a name?
لماذا يحتاج العبد إلى اسم؟
The arena owner called you No. 5,
لقد أطلق عليك مالك الساحة لقب رقم 5،
so I'll call you Five from now on.
لذا سأناديك بـ "خمسة" من الآن فصاعدًا.
Thank you, Master.
شكرا لك يا سيدي.
The snow...
الثلج...
In my past life,
في حياتي الماضية،
the first time I met Jun Che,
المرة الأولى التي التقيت فيها بجون تشي،
he made me kneel in the snow all night.
لقد جعلني أركع في الثلج طوال الليل.
If you want to thank me,
إذا كنت تريد أن تشكرني،
do it sincerely.
افعل ذلك بصدق.
Thank me on your knees.
اشكرني على ركبتيك.
Thank you, Master.
شكرا لك يا سيدي.
Shut up!
اسكت!
Yan Hui,
يان هوي,
I would be better off dead.
سيكون من الأفضل أن أموت.
I'm just like a walking corpse now.
أنا الآن مثل جثة تمشي.
Can Yan Hui bring you back from the dead?
هل يستطيع يان هوي إعادتك من الموت؟
If I catch you writing to another man again,
إذا وجدتك تكتب لرجل آخر مرة أخرى،
Let it go!
دعها تذهب!
I'll break your wings myself!
سأكسر جناحيك بنفسي!
My Lady, what happened?
سيدتي ماذا حدث؟
Bring me the horsewhip.
أحضر لي سوط الحصان.
You killed my pigeon,
لقد قتلت حمامتي
and prevented me from sending letters home.
ومنعتني من إرسال الرسائل إلى المنزل.
You imprisoned me while I was alive,
لقد سجنتني وأنا على قيد الحياة،
and wouldn't let me go even after I died.
ولم يسمحوا لي بالرحيل حتى بعد وفاتي.
Cutting you into a thousand pieces
تقطيعك إلى ألف قطعة
wouldn't ease the hatred in my heart.
لن يخفف الكراهية في قلبي.
Master, it's just a baby
سيدي، إنه مجرد طفل
and nearly freezing to death.
وكاد أن يموت من التجمد.
Please save it.
من فضلك احفظه.
Call someone.
اتصل بشخص ما.
Compared to my suffering,
بالمقارنة مع معاناتي،
this is merely a drop in the ocean.
هذا مجرد قطرة في المحيط.
I won't let you die easily.
لن أدعك تموت بسهولة.
[Lu's Mansion]
[قصر لو]
My Lady,
سيدتي،
he looks seriously injured.
يبدو أنه مصاب بجروح خطيرة.
Should we call a doctor?
هل يجب علينا استدعاء الطبيب؟
He defeated so many people.
لقد هزم الكثير من الناس.
He won't die easily.
لن يموت بسهولة.
But My Lady,
ولكن سيدتي،
your cloak is still on him.
لا يزال عباءتك عليه.
Should I get it back?
هل يجب علي أن استرجعه؟
He has made it dirty.
لقد جعلها قذرة.
Just leave it here.
فقط اتركه هنا.
So noisy.
صاخبة جداً.
[Those near are won over, and those far away come to join]
[يُقتَنَب القريبون، وينضم إليهم البعيدون]
Come on.
تعال.
Eat slowly.
تناول الطعام ببطء.
Come on, drink.
هيا اشرب.
You're annoying.
أنت مزعج.
I'm filthy rich.
أنا غني جداً.
Thank you, sir.
شكرا لك سيدي.
Murder!
قتل!
[Those near are won over, and those far away come to join]
[يُقتَنَب القريبون، وينضم إليهم البعيدون]
Chief Commander.
القائد الأعلى.
[Those near are won over, and those far away come to join]
[يُقتَنَب القريبون، وينضم إليهم البعيدون]
Get up.
استيقظ.
[Those near are won over, and those far away come to join]
[يُقتَنَب القريبون، وينضم إليهم البعيدون]
Chief Commander.
القائد الأعلى.
[Sang Li, a witch from Yue State and Jun Che's trusted aide]
[سانغ لي، ساحرة من ولاية يوي ومساعدة جون تشي الموثوقة]
Let us handle these scum.
دعونا نتعامل مع هذه الحثالة.
You don't have to deal with them yourself.
لا يتوجب عليك التعامل معهم بنفسك.
I've found a new hideout.
لقد وجدت مخبأ جديدا.
This arena is no longer useful.
هذه الساحة لم تعد مفيدة.
Sang Li, clean this place up thoroughly.
سانج لي، قم بتنظيف هذا المكان جيدًا.
The most important thing now
الشيء الأهم الآن
is to lie low
هو أن تختبئ
and bide our time.
وانتظر وقتنا.
[Wen, Jun Che's trusted aide]
[وين، مساعد جون تشي الموثوق]
People from all factions will gather
سيتجمع الناس من جميع الفصائل
at the Crown Prince's investiture ceremony.
في حفل تنصيب ولي العهد .
[Those near are won over, and those far away come to join]
[يُقتَنَب القريبون، وينضم إليهم البعيدون]
The situation will certainly be complex.
ومن المؤكد أن الوضع سيكون معقدا.
It's a perfect opportunity for us to observe covertly
إنها فرصة مثالية لنا للمراقبة سراً
and move in for the kill.
والتحرك نحو القتل.
Chief Commander.
القائد الأعلى.
Will you be staying
هل ستبقى؟
by that noble lady from the Lu family
من قبل تلك السيدة النبيلة من عائلة لو
to conceal your identity?
لإخفاء هويتك؟
Lu Yingying doesn't seem
لو ينغ ينغ لا يبدو
to be a docile lady.
أن تكون سيدة مطيعة.
Are you sure about this?
هل أنت متأكد من هذا؟
But I think
ولكنني أعتقد
she's quite interesting.
إنها مثيرة للاهتمام للغاية.
[Lu's Mansion]
[قصر لو]
Why did he recover so quickly?
لماذا تعافى بهذه السرعة؟
Where have you been?
أين كنت؟
Oh, it is here.
أوه، إنه هنا.
I've been looking for it everywhere.
لقد كنت أبحث عنه في كل مكان.
Why is there blood on your clothes?
لماذا يوجد دماء على ملابسك؟
It's from
إنه من
an old wound.
جرح قديم.
It's nothing.
لا شئ.
An old wound? Here?
جرح قديم؟ هنا؟
Does it hurt?
هل يؤلمك؟
Take off your clothes.
اخلع ملابسك.
Take it off!
إخلعها!